Search Menu

Lagged.com Privacy Policy & Terms of Use
========================================

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit https://lagged.com/ (the “Site”).

#### LIABILITY

All materials, information, software, products and services (also referred to as "Content"), included in or available through lagged.com (also referred to as "Site") are provided on an "as is" basis. The Content is provided without warranties of any kind.  
  
By using the Content of the Site, you explicitly agree to these terms and conditions. We do not warrant that the Content on this Site is accurate, reliable or correct; that this Site will be available at any particular time or location; that any defects or errors will be corrected; or that the Content is free of viruses or other harmful components. Your use of this Site is solely at your own risk. Any Content viewed, downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of this Site is done solely at your own discretion and risk, and you will be solely responsible for any damage, including without limitation personal injury or distress, damage to your computer system, or loss of data, that results from the viewing or download of any Content. The owner can not be held responsible for any problems occuring by using or not using the Site and its Content in any way.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as "Device Information."

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- "Cookies" are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

\- "Log files" track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

Additionally when you register an account on the Site, we collect your email address. A real and verified email address is not required to register an account. If you verify your email address we will opt you in to our weekly mailing list. You can opt out of the mailing list by clicking the unsubscribe button in the email, replying to the email directly or contact us using the information below.

When we talk about "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

#### SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](ttps://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

#### BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s ("NAI") educational page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work).

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

GOOGLE - [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous)

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

#### DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

#### YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

#### MINORS

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13.

#### CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

#### TERMS OF USE

Lagged and their affiliates are not responsible for anything that you upload, say or otherwise do at lagged.com. By using our site or registering at our site you agree to not upload any copyrighted material that you do not have the rights to, link to any inappropriate material and to be respectful in your interaction with other members.

This Site is offered and made available only to users thirteen (13) years of age or older. If you are not yet 13 years old or the required greater age for certain features, please discontinue using the Site immediately, or if for any reason, you do not agree with all of the terms and conditions contained in this Agreement, please discontinue using the Site immediately because by using or attempting to use the Site, you certify that you are at least 13 years of age (or other required greater age for certain features, where applicable) and meet any other eligibility requirements of the Site.

By using our website you agree to our terms of use and agree with our privacy policy.

#### CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [\[email protected\]](https://lagged.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Developer Terms
===============

By creating an account and/or submitting a game to lagged.app or lagged.com you agree to the following terms and conditions. All materials, information, software, products and services (also referred to as "Content"), included in or available through lagged.com (also referred to as "Site") are provided on an "as is" basis. The Content is provided without warranties of any kind.

By using the Content of the Site, you explicitly agree to these terms and conditions. We do not warrant that the Content on this Site is accurate, reliable or correct; that this Site will be available at any particular time or location; that any defects or errors will be corrected; or that the Content is free of viruses or other harmful components. Your use of this Site is solely at your own risk. Any Content viewed, downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of this Site is done solely at your own discretion and risk, and you will be solely responsible for any damage, including without limitation personal injury or distress, damage to your computer system, or loss of data, that results from the viewing or download of any Content. The owner can not be held responsible for any problems occuring by using or not using the Site and its Content in any way.

Developer is obligated to comply with Google's guidlines for publishers
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

View all guidlines here

* [https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/10502938?hl=en&ref\_topic=1250104#content](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/10502938?hl=en&ref_topic=1250104#content)

Child sexual abuse and exploitation
-----------------------------------

We do not allow content that:

* Sexually exploits or abuses children or content that promotes the sexual exploitation or abuse of children. This includes all child sexual abuse materials.
* Endangers children. Including but not limited to:
    * ‘Child grooming’ (for example, befriending a child online to facilitate, either online or offline, sexual contact and/or exchanging sexual imagery with that child);
    * ‘Sextortion’ (for example, threatening or blackmailing a child by using real or alleged access to a child’s intimate images);
    * Sexualization of a minor (for example, content that depicts, encourages or promotes the sexual abuse or exploitation of children); and
    * Trafficking of a child (for example, advertising or solicitation of a child for commercial sexual exploitation).

Dangerous or derogatory content
-------------------------------

We do not allow content that:

* incites hatred against, promotes discrimination of, or disparages an individual or group on the basis of their race or ethnic origin, religion, disability, age, nationality, veteran status, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, or other characteristic that is associated with systemic discrimination or marginalization.
    
    **Examples**: Promoting hate groups or hate group paraphernalia, encouraging others to believe that a person or group is inhuman, inferior, or worthy of being hated
    
* harasses, intimidates, or bullies an individual or group of individuals.
    
    **Examples**: Singling out someone for abuse or harassment, suggesting a tragic event did not happen or that victims or their families are actors or complicit in a cover-up of the event
    
* threatens or advocates for physical or mental harm to oneself or others.
    
    **Examples**: Content advocating suicide, anorexia, or other self-harm; threatening someone with real-life harm or calling for the attack of another person; promoting, glorifying, or condoning violence against others; content made by or in support of terrorist groups or transnational drug trafficking organizations, or content that promotes terrorist acts, including recruitment, or that celebrates attacks by transnational drug trafficking or terrorist organizations
    
* exploits others through extortion.
    
    **Examples**: Exploitative removals, revenge porn, blackmail

Misrepresentative content
-------------------------

### Misleading representation

We do not allow content that:

* misrepresents, misstates, or conceals information about the publisher, the content creator, the purpose of the content, or the content itself.
* falsely implies having an affiliation with, or endorsement by, another individual, organization, product, or service.
    
    **Examples**: Impersonating Google products, misusing company logos

### Unreliable and harmful claims

We do not allow content that:

* makes claims that are demonstrably false and could significantly undermine participation or trust in an electoral or democratic process.
    
    **Examples**: information about public voting procedures, political candidate eligibility based on age or birthplace, election results, or census participation that contradicts official government records
    
* promotes harmful health claims, or relates to a current, major health crisis and contradicts authoritative scientific consensus.
    
    **Examples**: Anti-vaccine advocacy, denial of the existence of medical conditions such as AIDS or Covid-19, gay conversion therapy
    
* contradicts authoritative scientific consensus on climate change.

### Deceptive practices

We do not allow:

* enticing users to engage with content under false or unclear pretenses.
* attempting to steal personal information or trick users into sharing personal information
    
    **Example**: Social engineering like phishing
    
* promoting content, products, or services using false, dishonest, or deceptive claims.
    
    **Examples**: "Get Rich Quick" schemes
    
* coordinating with other sites or accounts and concealing or misrepresenting your identity or other material details about yourself, where your content relates to politics, social issues or matters of public concern.
    
* directing content about politics, social issues, or matters of public concern to users in a country other than your own, if you misrepresent or conceal your country of origin or other material details about yourself.

### Manipulated media

We do not allow content that:

* deceives users through manipulated media related to politics, social issues, or matters of public concern.

Child friendly content
----------------------

All content must be child friendly:

* No adult themes
* No animal cruelty
* No sexually explicit content
* Is made to appear appropriate for a family audience, but contains adult themes including sex, violence, or other depictions of children or popular children’s characters that are unsuitable for a general audience.

Intellectual property abuse
---------------------------

We do not allow content that:

* infringes copyright. It is our policy to respond to notices of alleged infringement that comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA).
* sells or promotes the sale of counterfeit products. Counterfeit goods contain a trademark or logo that is identical to or substantially indistinguishable from the trademark of another. They mimic the brand features of the product in an attempt to pass themselves off as a genuine product of the brand owner.

View [Google Publisher Policies](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/10502938) for a full list of policies that your game must follow.

Deceptive implementation methods to obtain clicks or views
----------------------------------------------------------

We do not allow any deceptive ad practices including:

* Except for rewarded inventory, publishers may not ask others to click or view their ads or use deceptive implementation methods to obtain clicks or views. This includes, but is not limited to, offering compensation to users for viewing ads or performing searches, promising to raise money for third parties for such behavior or placing images next to individual ads.
* Any attempt aimed at artificially inflating the revenues accrued by Users through the Banners will automatically result in the removal of the game from the delivery of the Banners, the suspension of the User's account and, in case of recidivism, any report to the Public Authorities. By way of example but not limited to, it is forbidden to repeatedly click on your advertising elements, use systems for generating visits / clicks (autosurf, autohit, traffic exchange, etc.) on your games, clickjack and tamper with or modify the banner delivery codes.

#### Embed Game Terms of Use

Lagged allows other websites to embed certain games, but to embed any of our games you must embed exaclty the link provided in the embed games pop up. The embeded game must be linked direct and not under a game frame. You are not allowed to block links, block anayltics, block scripts or modify our code or games in any way. It is strictly prohibited to alter our games in any way or to embed our games in any way other than provided on our website. Websites enganged in gambling or illegal content or illegal activity are not allowed to embed our games in any way. Lagged provides the right to discontinue or alter our embeded games at any time. Lagged provides the right to request any website embeding our games to remove our games from their website.

Popular game categories
-----------------------

Games you might like
--------------------

[Troll Thief](https://lagged.com/en/g/troll-thief)  top rated

[Blob Opera](https://lagged.com/en/g/blob-opera)  top rated

[BitLife Life Simulator](https://lagged.com/en/g/bitlife-life-simulator)  top rated

[Slither 3D](https://lagged.com/en/g/slither-3d)  new

[All Games](https://lagged.com/all-games) · [Contact Us](https://lagged.com/contact) · [Developers](https://lagged.dev/) · [Privacy](https://lagged.com/privacy) · [Join our Discord](https://discord.com/invite/ncdDUwyk3W)

© Lagged 2024

English Nightmode
